const STORE = [
    {
        question: 'Why do we roast coffee?',

        answers: [
            'To make it more appealing to customers.',
            'To make it water soluble, and to expose flavors.',
            'To make it consumable by humans – it is poisonous when not roasted.',
            'To release caffeine molecules, making them absorbable to the human body.'
            ],
        correctAnswer: 1
    },
    {
        question: 'What is the difference between a <em>blend</em> and a <em>single origin</em>?',

        answers: [
            'All blends are comprised of many coffees, of which we cannot be sure of their origin, while a single origin comes from one farm. ',
            'Single origin coffees come only from Brazil.',
            'Blends are composed of more than one coffee, which on their own would be considered a single origin coffee. ',
            'Single origin coffees cannot be used for espresso, while blends can.'
        ],
        correctAnswer: 2
    },
    {
        question: 'What is RoR?',

        answers: [
        'Rotation of Rotor: This is our coffee roaster machine’s motor speed – important for determining how slowly or quickly we roast.',
        'Range of Reaction: A set time within our roast when certain chemical reactions occur – manipulating this time one way or the other will determine the final flavor of the coffee when brewed.',
        '<em>Rousche ofen Regler</em>: translated, *Rousche Regulator Oven* – named after chemist Ernst Rousche, this was the first roasting machine ever created, and is considered by many to be the most effective way to roast coffee.',
        'Rate of Rise: the calculated rate at which our bean mass temperature is rising, by a set interval.'
    ],
        correctAnswer: 3
    },
    {
        question: 'What are the Phases of a Roast?',

        answers: [
        'First, Middle, Final',
        'White, Green, Brown',
        'Green, Yellow, Dark',
        'Drying, Maillard, Development'
    ],
        correctAnswer: 0
    },
    {
        question: 'What is the <em>Maillard Reaction</em>?',

        answers: [
        'The scientific name for the entire roasting process.',
        'The term describing the delineation of chemicals when they’re roasted.',
        'The chemical reaction between an amino acid and a reducing sugar that causes the browning in all foods, tanning products, beer, condensed milk, etc.',
        'The reaction responsible for the caffeine content in an unroasted coffee seed.'
    ],
        correctAnswer: 2
    },
    {
        question: 'What is a cupping?',

        answers: [
        'When you have hot cups placed on your bare back, and removed after several minutes. While it does leave unsightly marks, it is known to remove toxins from the body.',
        'Any process of brewing coffee is technically considered cupping. ',
        'Setting freshly-roasted coffee out in a cup to de-gas so that we may measure their molecular makeup the next day.',
        'One of the processes which we use to make green coffee-buying decisions, perform quality control, and test new roast profile results.'
    ],
        correctAnswer: 3
    },
    {
        question: 'What is a roast profile?',

        answers: [
        'Everything that makes up how we roast a coffee – fan speed, gas pressure, time, resulting appearance, weight loss, etc.',
        'The information that we get from our importer telling us how to best roast this coffee.',
        'A dossier of where the coffee comes from, its specific growing parameters, moisture content, and intended use as a roasted product.',
        'Our instructions to our baristas and consumers about how to best brew a coffee that we’ve roasted.'
    ],
        correctAnswer: 0
    },
    {
        question: 'What is an accurate comparison of light roast and dark roast?',

        answers: [
        'Light roasts are typically more savory, best served with milk.',
        'The darker the coffee, the more sweetness and acidity can be tasted, while light roasts are generally flat and flavorless.',
        'Light roast is better because it undergoes more chemical reactions, creating a cleaner tasting result.',
        'Light roasts are roasted to a lighter color than dark roasts.'
    ],
        correctAnswer: 3
    },
    {
        question: 'What are the two most common ways of blending coffees?',

        answers: [
        '<em>Pre-roast Blending</em>, where we blend our coffees prior to roasting and roast them together; <em>Post-roast Blending</em>, where we blend coffees after we’ve roasted the individual coffees separately.',
        '<em>Mid-roast Blending</em>, where we roast to the mid-point time in our roast, then remove the coffee from the roaster. We do this for each coffee in the blend, then add them all together and roast again; <em>Factory Blending</em>, where we rely on the importer to blend the coffees for us.',
        '<em>Blind Blending</em>, where we blend random coffees every time, so there is never the same blend twice; <em>Calculated Blending</em>, where we weigh each of the coffees in the blend.',
        '<em>French Blending</em>, where we blend and roast the coffee twice; <em>Single Origin Blending</em>, where we take one single origin coffees and combine it with one or more others.'
    ],
        correctAnswer: 0
    },
    {
        question: 'What are we referring to when we’re talking about a coffee’s <em>density</em>?',

        answers: [
        'The level of perceived heaviness of the coffee on the palate after it is brewed.',
        'The measurement of the amount of coffee that can fit inside a beaker, expressed as mass divided by volume.',
        'The weight of the coffee after we roast it.',
        'The market share of that coffee’s origin compared to other origins.'
    ],
        correctAnswer: 1
    },
];
